ah nor speak not speak English no signal
here no sorry how you doing Thanks
so just a little minor housekeeping if
any banks creditors or utilities cloud
to see go speak English I don't know
Nancy here okay so here's your desk
great yeah cool so I'm I'm sure you've
worked as an assistant before yeah so
you know HootSuite slack Evernote
Outlook mm-hmm yeah yeah oh man is that
you yeah that was me on the cover of top
agent magazine in 1996 1996 oh and these
are that these are all the listings well
these are the unsalables these are the
listings so far gone that no one else
will take them on oh my god that looks
like the the Chinese deathtrap that is
the Chinese deathtrap no way the one
that housed all those like Hong Kong
crime organizations back in the day yeah
that and and there there is some
asbestos and some leaky pipes and
Cantonese goes how long have you had
that one just 16 years five months three
days but um yeah just take it a little
time anyways I'm gonna get going no
can't you enter these into Excel sure
yeah I can do that great well I'm gonna
take a break my first break in ten years
ten years Wow
yeah go go get him bye Nancy see you
soon
you
[Music]